SOLOMON IBIFUBARA BERNARD

1 kings close, sally best Lexim Estate, Abuja +2348165991753, +2349077622766. ibifubarabernard@protonmail.com 22nd July, 2000

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A highly motivated and hardworking Electrical and Electronics Engineering graduate with experience in Cybersecurity research, with sound interpersonal, learning and penetration testing skills, helping companies keep their valued software assets secured. I am keen to utilize and further develop my skills and knowledge in a value adding organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CyberSecurity Researcher Bug Bounty Hunter

(November 2022 - Date)

Using my skills in testing web applications, I have found over 30 valid vulnerabilities and bugs in the web applications of 10 different organizations across the World.

Creating programs to automate tasks using python.

Air Liquide Nigeria, Port Harcourt, Rivers State **Industrail Training.**

(June 2021 - August 2021)

Supervision of Electrical projects
Installation and maintenance of Electrical appliances
Maintenance of the Asu Plant
Assist the running of Acetylene Plant
Filling of gas cylinders

Candix Engineering, Port Harcourt, Rivers State Industrial Training

(May 2021 - June 2021)

Installation and Maintenance of street Lights

EDUCATION

Cross River University of Technology, Calabar. B.Eng Electrical and Electronics Engineering

(2023)

Midland International Christian Schools

West African Senior Secondary Certificate Examination WASSCE

(2016)

Core Skills

Result oriented, excellent interpersonal, verbal and written communication skills.

Ethical Hacking

Proficient in Linux Operating System

Proficient in Web application testing tools, BurpSuite, Zaproxy

Proficient in writing work reports

Fundamental or Basic knowledge in Python, Javascript, Css, Html, pHp, Sql and Networking.

Good planning and a strong goal achiever with excellent organizational skills.

The ability to plan, schedule and prioritize workloads with organizational skills.

Strong work ethics, good leadership and management skills

Good team player, confident and focused

Exceptional analytical, problem-solving skills and reasoning ability.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hall of Fame for Most Accepted Bug for a Company (2023)